much be made or on its way. My guess is
I guess we're not very many weeks away from being able to do that.
been able to supply you with either the FTX
much be made or on its way. My guess is
做很多事情或正在途中。我的猜测是
been able to supply you with either the FTX
能够为您提供FTX
x1 field or the FTX.
x1字段或FTX。
x1 optimum. So if you
x1最佳。所以，如果你
So if you're interested in this transceiver, now is the time to go.
因此，如果您对该收发器感兴趣，那么现在是时候了。
Now is the time to give us a call and say you're ready.
现在是时候给我们打电话并说您准备好了。
to say you are interested, register your interest and
要说您有兴趣，请注册您的利息和
and we will make sure you're on the list. We don't have covers.
我们将确保您在列表中。我们没有封面。
We don't take deposits because we don't want to be in a situation
我们不拿存款，因为我们不想处于这种情况
fawr am un o'od NHG.
非常适合其中一个NHG。
bod我有었de gen yn dim ar gyur a'r fynd omur i yna f worksi ie.cioawrym pie i labes Roeddon
We'd much rather you come to us and say look I'm enjoying it.
look I'm interested I'd like to buy from you because you
because you've been going for 50 odd years, Peter.
bod我有었de gen yn dim ar gyur a'r fynd omur i yna f worksi ie.cioawrym pie i labes Roeddon
boody zen nur fdus oiur fdus omur folkie i ie.ciavrym pie.city pie i labes roedder
and you've done a lot of the harm radio blah blah blah
blah blah blah, except you may not think that way of course.
而且你做了很多伤害收音机等等等等
等等，等等，除了您当然不会这样认为。